Two more for us, huh?
Oh, there's a good boy.
Here you go.
I was starting to think you would never calm down.
Are you brothers?
Same age, so possibly twins as well.
No, they're neither.
This one here is sweet and well-behaved.
And this one, well, he's a bit spirited.
Then there's the fact that they don't look a thing alike.
Hmm, you know.
Hmm, now, for this spirited little thing...
Ow!
Ow, a bit too spirited.
Asta, huh?
Well, you've had a tough beginning, but your worries are over.
As of today, boys, this will be your home.
Asta and Yuno.
With all this work, I sure hope we have a good harvest.
Yeah, same here.
What's that about?
That kid from the church is at it again.
One day, I'll be the Wizard King!
And I'll make you the happiest woman in the world!
That's why I'm asking, will you please marry me?
I'm sorry, Asta.
I just can't.
It's my duty to serve everyone.
That's a no!
Yes, it is.
I can't marry you.
I'm not giving up yet!
You should, really.
Please, Asta.
Not giving up!
I'm truly sorry!
Please, Sister Lily, just let me ask one more time!
No!
Water creation magic is my best of love!
I'm so sorry, Asta.
I wasn't thinking.
My magic just slipped out.
Nice, Sister.
Way to go.
Show him no mercy.
But I didn't mean to.
We're not done here!
Come on.
How many times does she have to turn you down?
Why are you sticking your nose in this, Yuno?
That's simple, really.
Because you're noisy, you're short.
You lack both composure and tolerance.
And there's not really anything about you that appeals to women.
Hey!
Fifteen years of growing up together and that's how you talk to me?
You big lady killing jerk!
May I help?
Thank you, Yuno.
You think you can just ignore me?
Asta.
Nuns are women of the cloth, which means they can't marry.
Neither can fifteen-year-old boys, in fact.
Think you're so smart.
Well, I'll show you.
Yeah, I will.
You and me, right here, right now!
Not today.
And why the hell not, huh?
It'll be a waste of time.
What'd you say to me?
Give it a rest already, Yasta.
There's no way you stand a chance against him and you know it.
Take this!
And...
This is pointless.
Kill!
You know that you can't use magic.
Oh, what?
Come on!
Still nothing?
Why?
You're funny, Yasta!
It is pretty crazy.
Not being able to use any kind of magic at his age?
That never happens.
What's your deal, huh?
I'm older than you, kid!
Show some respect!
Not a chance.
Haven't you figured out that in this world, magic is everything?
It's not a matter of whether you have it, but how much.
You're the only person I've ever heard of who can't use any magic at all.
All right, then.
Looks like I'm gonna have to bust out my secret moves.
You've got secret moves?
Bet you can't do crunches this fast!
Like anyone cares, idiot.
I'm just getting money again!
Look at that!
You look amazing!
This is nothing for him.
Such a big help, thank you.
All right!
Leave the wood chopping to me!
I've got this covered!
Oh, jeez.
They're really the same age?
You definitely can't tell it from the way they act.
Yuno is the hope of this church!
Getting into the magic knights isn't just a silly dream for Yuno.
He'll make it for sure.
The awarding of the grimoires is coming up.
Once you have yours, things will change.
Just wait and see, Asta.
You'll be able to use magic in no time at all.
Thank you so much, Sister Lily.
Well, probably anyway.
My grimoire.
I'll have it soon.
Finally.
That's right!
I'm going to get the most awesome grimoire ever!
I'll join up with the magic knights,
and once I make a name for myself,
I'll follow in your footsteps and become the wizard king!
He'll never give up this nonsense, will he?
And then I'll come back and rebuild this crumbling dump of a church!
Crumbling dump!
That's taking it too far!
Isn't that right, Yuno?
Huh?
I'll show all of you.
I swear, just watch and you'll see, damn you!
Asta, wait!
Really?
How am I younger than him?
Hey, Yuno?
Do you think you could maybe try to get along a little better with Asta?
I mean, like you used to back when you were younger.
You two were always together.
Yuno used to be such a crybaby.
But then one day,
he came back with Asta,
who was badly injured.
And since then,
I haven't seen him cry once.
What's the point?
There's no getting along with that one.
Now that I think about it,
they were both different afterwards.
That's when Asta started coming home covered in mud every day.
I wonder where he goes off to and what he's doing.
994,
995,
996,
997,
998,
999!
And now for some magic-enhancing mogul leaf juice.
Bottoms up!
I will be the Wizard King.
Nothing's going to stop me.
And the first step is getting my body trained up!
March.
When the Firefly Dandelions float through the air,
once a year throughout the Clover Kingdom,
those children who have reached 15 years of age
gather for the Grimoire Acceptance Ceremony,
a rite of passage that will increase their magical power.
Awesome!
Are all these shelves filled with Grimoires?
Which one is mine?
Once I get my hands on a Grimoire,
I'm going to be able to use magic too.
I'll catch up to you soon enough, you know.
Hmm.
The day that I'll become a full-fledged mage,
it's about time.
Look what the cat dragged in.
Could they be any shabbier?
We shouldn't have to give Grimoires to anyone
who just walks in off the street.
Makes me sick to my stomach.
You don't think the pathetic creatures
would be foolish enough to attempt
the Magic Knight's entrance exam in six months, do you?
Only high-ranking nobles and royalty
have enough innate magic power to pass the exam.
See the shrimpy one?
I heard that he can't use magic at all.
Oh, wow.
We'd better take extra special care of him.
I mean, he's one of a kind.
The only person in the entire country
who can't use magic.
Welcome to Grimoire Tower,
except he's.
On this momentous day,
you will take your first step down a new path.
I wish you integrity, hope, and love.
For those who don't know,
I am the master of this Grimoire Tower.
Now, never once has anyone from this region
distinguished him or herself
by becoming a magic knight,
much less the wizard king.
I pray that one among you
will have what it takes
to become the most powerful mage in the land.
Seriously, I mean it!
And now,
to accept
your Grimoires.
Finally,
my very own Grimoire.
Check it out.
Mine's bigger than yours.
Yeah, maybe,
but mine's thicker.
Here it is.
My one-way ticket
out of this little village.
I could carry on
the family business.
But this is my Grimoire?
Seriously?
Why is mine so tiny?
I guess
I'll decide what to do
once there are more pages of magic in here.
Six months from now,
we'll be taking
the prestigious magic knight's entrance exam.
And we'll pass it, too.
Just wait.
Yes, very good.
I have high hopes for you.
Hey, uh...
Is my Grimoire
running late
or something?
Hey, uh...
Is my Grimoire
running late
or something?
Uh...
Try again next year?
What?
Oh, wow.
Are you kidding?
That's actually kind of awesome.
What?
That is too funny.
Seriously?
That's awful.
I can't believe it.
Ha!
Well, he's got us beat
in one area anyway.
Complete and utter uselessness.
Oh!
The Fourleaf Clover?
What?
The Fourleaf?
Like out of the legend?
Really?
The Grimoire that was bestowed
upon the first Wizard King?
If the stories about it are true,
it's imbued not only with
tremendous power
but also good luck.
And it's his?
A filthy little commoner?
Awesome!
I will
become the Wizard King.
Amazing!
He's the brightest star of the whole village of Hajj!
You're amazing, you!
He's so cool!
You know, just wait.
I'm hot on your heels.
I'll catch up to you!
I am your rival!
His rival?
Who does he think he is?
Talk to some idiot who didn't even get a Grimoire!
No.
Well, everyone, time to go!
We've got a lot of preparations to make for the big banquet.
Good!
Since today's special, you all get three pot potatoes a piece!
I hate you!
Maybe we could have something different for a change?
Well, isn't this extraordinary?
A boy wonder, and from a sleepy little village, too.
I was so sure.
All this time, I just needed a Grimoire, and then I'd finally be able to use magic.
And now, to not even get a Grimoire...
No!
I won't give up that easily!!
Ha ha ha ha! You're not winning this round, Fate! Don't underestimate me!
It doesn't matter if it takes a year or two or ten or a hundred! I don't care! I'll work till I get that grimoire!
I will become the Wizard King! I'll prove anyone can be great! Even a poor commoner who was abandoned at birth!
Take that! Ha ha! And just you wait, you know!
Hey, isn't that going a bit too far? We were supposed to be the stars of the show today!
He ruined that! A low-life commoner! And he got the four-leaf clover! I need to make him pay!
Wait! I'll burn that book till it's nothing but ash!
He dispelled my flames without even using his grimoire!
Go on! You try!
What?
Do it!
We can't have that getting all burned up now, can we?
Resisting would be a foolish waste of your time. My magic binding iron chain formation spell blocks its captive's movement and magic!
What do you want? Who are you?
I suppose a village boy wouldn't know, but until very recently, I was relatively well known among the Magic Knight squads as Chain Magic Revchi.
But they expelled me from their illustrious ranks, and now I am not but a humble thief!
So if you'll excuse me, I'll be taking this grimoire of yours!
You said that your name was Revchi? Why bother stealing it? There's no point.
Grimoires must be used by their chosen masters!
Yes, village boy, I'm well aware.
That said, there are plenty of black market collectors who would pay a small fortune in exchange for such a unique specimen!
The four-leaf clover may have chosen you, but you only received it! An untrained novice! A mere hatchling!
This is not your lucky day. Such a pity for you I happen to be here. Your legend is over.
Before it even began.
Oh-ho! I bet that pendant would fetch a good price. Don't mind if I do-
Hold it!
AHHHHHH!
What the hell is going on here?!
I've come to rescue-
Eh?
Hey, creep, what's your deal?
That's Uno's grimoire you've got.
What are you doing with it?
You dirty rotten thief!
rotten thief why look it's the sad little boy who waited so long but never got a grimoire oh you've
heard of me yeah you're right the poor empty-handed kill the only place a grimoire belongs is with its
true master now give that back to you know you really are a sheltered creature if you believe
that kind of reasoning will get you anywhere with the likes of me allow me to disabuse you of that
kosher us to run from a waste of space like him not a chance in hell
i'll get you no boy you're finished here
dance of the pitless viper
that's one serious attack
so this is what mages outside the village can do
even as much as i've trained my body i don't stand a chance you see boy it's no use thanks for playing
though it's not over i'm not done i will be the wizard king the wizard king you're joking
the thing is these chains can measure the magic power of anyone they come in contact with
and you have none not a single drop you were probably born that way i guess this explains why
you didn't get a grimoire to possess not the slightest bit of magic in a world where magic is everything
why that makes you a rare and precious bird indeed
if that's true then no matter how hard i push myself i'll never be able to use magic
you know i really can't think of anything more pitiful forget about becoming the wizard king you'll
be lucky to just get a job i bet your friend the genius over there is having a good laugh at your
expense right about now yeah maybe you know so great the four leaf clover chose him then there's
me this world is no use for someone like you a poor magicless fool you might as well give it all up
right now you were born a loser you worthless front yeah he's right no matter how hard i try
i guess there are some things that just aren't possible
so i might as well give hey who are you calling a loser asta it's true that you aren't going to become
the wizard king not ever you hear that even your little friend knows that it's impossible
that's because i am going to be the wizard king
what you're wrong about asta revji
very wrong asta's no loser he's my rival
huh this is who you would claim as your rival the only person in the world without magic
you get off of me
sorry you had to see me at such a weak moment you know
just give me a second that's all then i'll destroy this guy
is that a grim bar i knew it like you wouldn't be chosen asta there's no way
is that your magic
but i checked and you didn't have any magic power how could you be granted a grim war
the leaves of a clover are said to each contain one thing in the first three dwell integrity hope and love
the fourth leaf is given over to good luck
and in the fifth
in the fifth
there live the devil
The same thing that he says to her
Is that a word that is because it will be a bit less
Can I hear this?
the how to do it
君どこまでも 泡かけたらない いつの日も 夢見てた それでも一方一方しかない 世界でも何度も倒れたベッド 本能のまま 諦めちゃいけた
THE END
Thank you.